

Hakeem I. Animashaun

143 Dipo olubi street, Surulere, Lagos state.

+2347063636703

hakeemanimashaunsnr@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hakeem-animashaun-b1600715a https://github.com/hakeemanimashaun?tab=repositories

Adaptable professional with years of experience and a passion for creating user-friendly, highly functional,, and visually appealing mobile applications. I deliver high quality code that can be easily managed over a long period. I have proven leadership knowledge, problem-solving, and workflow prioritization in android native and react native roles.

Educational Background

University of Lagos

Bachelor's Degree: Metallurgical and

materials engineering

2019

Certificates

- Jobberman Soft skills Certification: 2021
- Scrum Expert Certification 2021
- Oracle professional certification:
- SQL expert certification: 2013

Work Experience

Mobile Developer

Standard Bank(Stanbic-IBTC) July 2022 to February 2023

Contributed to a 6 module mega banking application with each service modularized and easily seperatable into a stand alone application. services: insurance, ease, banking, pension, SME, Mutual funds.

Mobile Lead developer

Aladdin Digital Bank

April 2022 to August 2022

Transformed the loan application into a community for businesses with in app banking services and an escrow system. integrated other loan features eg. travel loans.

Android Developer

Decagon Institute

March 2021 to April 2022

Delivered standard android native code using Kotlin and employing MVVM and MVC architectures to maage code structure.

Project Links

Stanbic IBTC Mobile App

android: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?

id=com.stanbicibtc.mobile&hl=en&gl=US

iOS: https://apps.apple.com/ng/app/stanbic-ibtc-mobile-

app/id1167007240

Aladdin Digital

android: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?
id=com.aladdin.digital&hl=en&gl=US

iOS:

https://apps.apple.com/ng/app/aladdin-digital/id1604858307

Ricive Merchant

android: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=com.ricive.ricivelaundry&hl=en&gl=US iOS: https://apps.apple.com/ng/app/ricive-merchant/id1618944180

MobilFind

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=com.decagon.mobifind&hl=en&gl=US

Volunteer Work

PSP Supervisor : LAWMA march 2021 to October 2021

Supervised Psp operators as they collect and dispose of environmental waste within ikeja axis of Lagos state.

Skills & Proficiencies

- Process Flows
- Android native
- React native
- kotlin
- Typescript
- Git
- Code architecture
- Effective communication
- firebase
- Jest
- Expresso
- J-unit
- Google cloud console